<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<languagepack xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="http://www.vstechnology.net/schemas/languagepack.xsd">  
	<info id="en" name="English" brand="GTS" product="Santa Surprise" debug="false" version="$Id: vgtemplate_en.xml 26636 2007-12-04 14:49:59Z daram $" signedoff="false"/>  
	<!-- Start generic static text -->  
	<multitext id="1" qa="true" text="Connecting to server..."/>  
	<multitext id="2" qa="true" text="Connection failed"/>  
	<multitext id="3" qa="true" text="Loading"/>  
	<multitext id="4" qa="true" text="Loading complete"/>  
	<multitext id="5" qa="true" text="Help"/>  
	<multitext id="6" qa="true" text="Close"/>  
	<multitext id="7" qa="true" text="Balance"/>  
	<multitext id="8" qa="true" text="Stake"/>  
	<multitext id="9" qa="true" text="Odds"/>  
	<multitext id="10" qa="true" text="Win"/>  
	<multitext id="11" qa="true" text="To Win"/>  
	<multitext id="12" qa="true" text="OK"/>  
	<multitext id="13" qa="true" text="Prize Table"/>  
	<multitext id="14" qa="true" text="Play"/>  
	<multitext id="15" qa="true" text="Go"/>  
	<multitext id="16" qa="true" text="BET"/>  
	<multitext id="17" qa="true" text="Submit"/>  
	<multitext id="18" qa="true" text="Submit Bet"/>  
	<multitext id="19" qa="true" text="Submit All Bets"/>  
	<multitext id="20" qa="true" text="Cashout"/>  
	<multitext id="21" qa="true" text="Return"/>  
	<multitext id="22" qa="true" text="Bank"/>  
	<multitext id="23" qa="true" text="Bonus"/>  
	<multitext id="24" qa="true" text="Total Stake"/>  
	<multitext id="25" qa="true" text="Max. Return"/>  
	<multitext id="26" qa="true" text="Max. Win"/>  
	<multitext id="27" qa="true" text="Jackpot"/>  
	<multitext id="28" qa="true" text="Play Again"/>  
	<multitext id="29" qa="true" text="Please try again"/>  
	<multitext id="30" qa="true" text="Play for Fun"/>  
	<multitext id="31" qa="true" text="Play for Real"/>  
	<multitext id="32" qa="true" text="Game Over"/>  
	<multitext id="33" qa="true" text="Cancel"/>  
	<multitext id="34" qa="true" text="Clear All"/>  
	<multitext id="35" qa="true" text="To play this game you require the latest version Flash Player. Please click the link below and follow the quick and simple installation instructions."/>  
	<multitext id="36" qa="true" text="Get flash player"/>  
	<multitext id="37" qa="true" text="Jackpots"/>  
	<multitext id="38" qa="true" text="Note that any Jackpots are shown and paid in your account currency."/>  
	<!-- End generic static text -->  
	<!-- Start game specific text [ Begin @id=100 ] -->  
	<!-- Game Console -->  
	<multitext id="101" qa="true" text="INFO"/>  
	<multitext id="103" qa="true" text="LINES"/>  
	<multitext id="104" qa="true" text="-"/>  
	<multitext id="105" qa="true" text="+"/>  
	<multitext id="106" qa="true" text="BET MAX"/>  
	<multitext id="107" qa="true" text="SPIN"/>  
	<multitext id="108" qa="true" text="STOP"/>  
	<multitext id="109" qa="true" text="TOTAL BET"/>  
	<multitext id="110" qa="true" text="LINE BET"/>  
	<multitext id="111" qa="true" text="WIN"/>  
	<multitext id="112" qa="true" text="GAMBLE"/>  
	<multitext id="115" qa="true" text="AUTO START"/>  
	<multitext id="116" qa="true" text="STOP"/>  
	<multitext id="117" qa="true" text="-"/>  
	<multitext id="118" qa="true" text="+"/>  
	<multitext id="119" qa="true" text="SPINS"/>  
	<multitext id="120" qa="true" text="CLICK TO START"/>  
	<!-- Information -->  
	<multitext id="125" qa="true" text="SHOW PAYLINES"/>  
	<multitext id="126" qa="true" text="HIDE PAYLINES"/>  
	<multitext id="127" qa="true" text="BACK"/>  
	<!--multitext id="140" qa="true" text="ONLY HIGHEST WIN PAYS PER LINE WIN COMBINATIONS PAY LEFT TO RIGHT ONLY EXCEPT SCATTER WHICH PAYS ANY  PAYLINE WINS ARE MULTIPLIED BY THE LINE BET  MALFUNCTIONS VOID ALL PLAYS AND PAYS "/-->  
	<multitext id="140" qa="true" text="ONLY HIGHEST WIN PAYS PER LINE. WIN COMBINATIONS PAY LEFT TO RIGHT ONLY EXCEPT"/>  
	<multitext id="141" qa="true" text="PAYLINE WINS ARE MULTIPLIED BY THE LINE BET. MALFUNCTIONS VOID ALL PLAYS AND PAYS"/>  
	<multitext id="142" qa="true" text="WHICH PAYS ANY"/>  
	<multitext id="150" qa="true" text="WILD"/>  
	<multitext id="151" qa="true" text="SUBSTITUTES FOR ALL SYMBOLS EXCEPT SCATTER AND BONUS"/>  
	<multitext id="152" qa="true" text="BONUS"/>  
	<multitext id="154" qa="true" text="SCATTER"/>  
	<multitext id="155" qa="true" text="10&#10;X3"/>  
	<multitext id="156" qa="true" text="FREE GAMES&#10;MULTIPLIER"/>  
	<multitext id="158" qa="true" text="CHRISTMAS GIFTS"/>  
	<multitext id="170" qa="true" text="FREE GAMES"/>  
	<multitext id="171" qa="true" text="ALL WINS IN FREE GAMES ARE TRIPLED EXCEPT FOR THE CHRISTMAS GIFTS BONUS&#10;&#10;3 OR MORE SCATTER WINS 10 MORE FREE GAMES &#10;&#10;FREE GAMES CAN BE PLAYED INFINITELY"/>  
	<multitext id="172" qa="true" text="ANYWHERE WINS 10 FREE GAMES"/>  
	<multitext id="180" qa="true" text="CHRISTMAS GIFTS BONUS"/>  
	<multitext id="181" qa="true" text="OR MORE"/>  
	<multitext id="182" qa="true" text="3 OR MORE CONSECUTIVE BONUS ON AN ACTIVE &#10;PAYLINE STARTING WITH THE LEFTMOST REEL STARTS THE CHRISTMAS GIFT BONUS &#10;&#10;SANTA HAS LEFT YOU 6 GIFTS TO CHOOSE FROM&#10;&#10;IF 3, 4 OR 5 BONUS TRIGGERED THE BONUS GAME, CHOOSE 3, 4 OR 5 GIFTS FOR CASH PRIZES ACCORDINGLY"/>  
	<!-- PROMO MESSAGES  -->  
	<multitext id="201" qa="true" text="WINS 10000X LINE BET!"/>  
	<multitext id="202" qa="true" text="WINS 500X TOTAL BET!"/>  
	<multitext id="203" qa="true" text="ANYWHERE STARTS FREE GAMES!"/>  
	<multitext id="204" qa="true" text="3 OR MORE"/>  
	<multitext id="205" qa="true" text="ON ACTIVE PAYLINES"/>  
	<multitext id="206" qa="true" text="STARTS CHRISTMAS GIFT BONUS!"/>  
	<multitext id="207" qa="true" text="5X"/>  
	<multitext id="208" qa="true" text="WINS 10 FREE GAMES"/>  
	<multitext id="209" qa="true" text="WITH X3 MULTIPLIER"/>  
	<multitext id="210" qa="true" text="5 OF A KIND!"/>  
	<multitext id="211" qa="true" text="WINS"/>  
	<multitext id="212" qa="true" text="FREE GAMES"/>  
	<multitext id="213" qa="true" text="10 MORE FREE GAMES!"/>  
	<!--  BONUS SCREEN -->  
	<multitext id="225" qa="true" text="BONUS WIN"/>  
	<multitext id="226" qa="true" text="PICK 5 GIFTS TO WIN CASH PRIZES!"/>  
	<multitext id="227" qa="true" text="PICK 4 GIFTS TO WIN CASH PRIZES!"/>  
	<multitext id="228" qa="true" text="PICK 3 GIFTS TO WIN CASH PRIZES!"/>  
	<multitext id="229" qa="true" text="PICK 2 GIFTS TO WIN CASH PRIZES!"/>  
	<multitext id="230" qa="true" text="PICK 1 GIFT TO WIN CASH PRIZE!"/>  
	<multitext id="231" qa="true" text="SANTA HAS LEFT GIFTS!"/>  
	<!--  FREE GAME SELECTION SCREEN -->  
	<multitext id="252" qa="true" text="YOU WIN"/>  
	<multitext id="253" qa="true" text="FREE GAMES"/>  
	<multitext id="254" qa="true" text="X3 MULTIPLIER"/>  
	<multitext id="255" qa="true" text="MORE FREE GAMES"/>  
	<multitext id="256" qa="true" text="WITH"/>  
	<!--  FREE GAME SCREEN -->  
	<multitext id="281" qa="true" text="SPINS LEFT"/>  
	<multitext id="282" qa="true" text="FREE GAMES WIN"/>  
	<multitext id="283" qa="true" text="MULTIPLIER"/>  
	<multitext id="284" qa="true" text="X3"/>  
	<!--  FEATURE WIN POPUP -->  
	<multitext id="291" qa="true" text="GAME WIN"/>  
	<multitext id="292" qa="true" text="FEATURE WIN"/>  
	<multitext id="293" qa="true" text="TOTAL WIN"/>  
	<multitext id="294" qa="true" text="CONTINUE"/>  
	<!-- End game specific text -->  
	<!-- Start generic phrases -->  
	<phrase id="BetUnavailable" qa="true" text="Error"/>  
	<phrase id="BetUnavailableBody" qa="true" text="This bet is not currently available."/>  
	<phrase id="BetterLuckButton" qa="true" text="OK"/>  
	<phrase id="BetterLuckTitle" qa="true" text="Play Again?"/>  
	<phrase id="Congratulations" qa="true" text="Congratulations!"/>  
	<phrase id="CongratulationsBody" qa="true" text="You have won %1!"/>  
	<phrase id="CongratulationsHandBody" qa="true" text="You have won %1 with a %2."/>  
	<phrase id="CongratulationsButton" qa="true" text="OK"/>  
	<phrase id="Connecting" qa="true" text="Connecting to server"/>  
	<phrase id="ErrorRetrievingAccount" qa="true" text="There has been an error retrieving your previous game, please refresh"/>  
	<phrase id="ExceedingMaxWinBody" qa="true" text="You have exceeded the maximum possible winning limit for any one bet. Please change your bet or cashout."/>  
	<phrase id="ExceedingMaxWinTitle" qa="true" text="Maximum winning limit"/>  
	<phrase id="FunRealAnon" qa="true" text="Play for fun. If you would like to Play for Real, please log into or create an account."/>  
	<phrase id="GameInProgressBody" qa="true" text="You are part way through a game. Please click to resume."/>  
	<phrase id="GameInProgressTitle" qa="true" text="Game in progress"/>  
	<phrase id="Help" qa="true" text="SANTA SURPRISE&#10;5-Reel 20-line Slots&#10;The objective of Santa Surprise is to obtain winning symbol combinations by spinning the reels. &#10; &#10; &#10;TO PLAY THE GAME: &#10; &#10;* Paylines are chosen by clicking Lines. Each click activates a payline. When all paylines are activated, clicking the button again resets it to one active payline. Paylines can also be activated by using the numbered buttons on either side of the reels. Selecting a high payline includes all the lower ones too. For example, selecting payline 6 also activates paylines 1 through 5. Clicking Bet Max activates all paylines with the current bet per line and spins the reels.  &#10; &#10;* Total bet per game round = line bet X active paylines.  &#10; &#10;* Clicking Spin spins the reels with the current selection of lines and line bets. During the reel spins the Spin button changes into Stop. Clicking Stop ends the spin animation and immediately displays the spin result.  &#10; &#10;* Reels can also be spun using the Auto Start function. Clicking + or - above Auto Start selects the successive number of spins to be enabled. Clicking Auto Start spins the reels. The Auto Start button changes into Stop during the Auto Start mode of reelspin. The Auto Start mode ends when the reels have been spun the number of times determined by the player, or when the player clicks Stop. &#10; &#10; * Wins are calculated according to the paytable. Line win = line bet X corresponding multiplier according to the paytable. Scatter win = total bet X corresponding multiplier according to the paytable. The paytable can be accessed via the Info page. When opened after a winning spin, the winning symbol combinations (number of symbols and bet multiplier) are highlighted and blink. &#10; &#10;* On a given payline, only the highest payline winning combination pays while simultaneous winnings on different paylines are accumulated.  &#10; &#10;* In case of a winning spin, the Win field displays the accumulating winnings. The Win ticker can be stopped by clicking anywhere on the screen to display the total win amount immediately.  &#10; &#10;* Payline wins and the total win are also displayed on the black strip located at the bottom of the game window.&#10; &#10; &#10;INFO PAGE:&#10;Clicking Info opens the reference screen describing different game components. Clicking the arrow buttons at the lower right-hand corner of the screen enables navigating between the different info screens. &#10; &#10;* The Paytable screen shows all winning combinations. When opened after a winning spin, the winning symbol combinations (number of symbols and bet multiplier) are highlighted and blink. &#10; &#10; * The Christmas Gifts Bonus screen describes the symbol combinations necessary to enter the Bonus game and describes the Christmas Gifts Bonus game rules.  &#10; &#10;* The Free Games screen describes the symbol combinations necessary to enter the Free Games feature and describes the Free Games feature rules.&#10; &#10;* Clicking Show Paylines on the Paytable page, opens a screen that illustrates all possible payline combinations. Clicking Hide Paylines closes this screen and returns to the Paytable page.  &#10; &#10;* Clicking Back exits the Info screen and returns to the game.  &#10; &#10; &#10;PAYLINES:  &#10; &#10;* Active paylines are represented by lines that appear over the reels. Paylines can be activated and their shape displayed by progressively clicking Lines.  &#10; &#10;* Only active paylines can register wins.  &#10; &#10;* There is a difference between the line bet and the total bet. The line bet shows how much is being bet on a single payline. The total bet shows how much is being bet in total on the game round. Payouts shown in the paytable are multiplied by the line bet.  The Scatter symbol is an exception to these rules. More information about the Scatter symbol can be found below.  &#10; &#10;About payouts: &#10;* Payouts are listed on the Paytable screen. To find the possible win amount, the line bet must be multiplied by the payout.  &#10;* If two payline winning combinations occur on the same line, the higher of them is paid out. If more than one active payline has a winning combination, the winnings are accumulated.  &#10;* Winning combinations must start from the left most reel, and the symbols have to be consecutive.  The Scatter symbol is an exception to these rules. More information about the Scatter symbol can be found below.  &#10; &#10; &#10;WILD SYMBOL &#10;The Wild symbol in the game is the Santa symbol. It can stand for any other symbol, except Scatter and Bonus, to make the best possible winning combination. There is also a separate payout for two or more Wild symbols on an active payline, as seen in the Paytable. This is paid out instead of the regular symbol win if the win amount from Wilds is larger than the win from the regular symbols (by Wild standing in).  &#10; &#10; &#10;SCATTER SYMBOL&#10; The Scatter symbols in the game are the house symbols. They do not have to occur on any particular payline. If there are two or more Scatters anywhere on the reels, in any position, in the spin results, the payout earned is multiplied by the total bet and added to payline winnings. If three or more Scatter symbols appear anywhere on the reels, in any position, simultaneously, the player wins 10 Free Games with multiplier X3 for all wins during the Free Games, except for the Bonus game wins.   &#10; &#10; &#10;BONUS SYMBOL&#10;The Bonus symbols in the game are the Christmas Tree with the word BONUS on them. If three or more Bonus symbols appear consecutively on an active payline, starting with the leftmost reel, the Christmas Gifts Bonus is triggered.  &#10; &#10; &#10;CHRISTMAS GIFTS BONUS &#10;To start the Christmas Gifts Bonus round, click on Click to Start.  In the Christmas Gifts Bonus, the player has to pick 3 to 5 presents out of 6. The number of presents to pick is equal to the number of Bonus symbols that triggered the Bonus round. Clicking on a selection wins a cash prize.  At the end of the Bonus game, a win screen displays your winnings. Click Continue to return to the regular slot reels.   &#10; &#10; &#10;FREE GAMES &#10;3 or more Scatters anywhere on the reels trigger 10 Free Games with multiplier X3 for all wins during the Free Games, except for the Christmas Gifts Bonus wins. A multiplier means that when it is in effect, the win is multiplied by that number.  To start the Free Games, click on Click to Start. A message will appear detailing the number of Free Games and multiplier won. After a short pause, the Free Games begin automatically. During the Free Games, the reels are spun automatically using the same number of lines and bets per line as on the spin that won the Free Games. After each spin, the win is displayed in the Win field. The Free Games Win field shows the accumulated winnings from the current Free Games. After all Free Games have been completed, a result board summarizes the winnings. Game Win shows the winnings that were received from the spin that won the free games. Feature Win shows the winnings that were received from the free spins. Total Win shows the accumulated winnings (Game Win and Feature Win added up). Clicking Continue will return you to the regular slot reels. When returning to the main game, clicking anywhere on the screen stops the win ticker and displays the full prize. If 3 or more Scatter symbols appear anywhere on the reels, in any combination, during Free Games, 10 additional Free Games are added to the existing ones with the same multiplier.  Free Game wins are added to the payline and Scatter wins.  If the Free Games are triggered during the Auto Start mode, the feature begins after the player clicks on Click to Start. When all Free Games have been played and the player clicks Continue on the screen summarizing the Free Games win, the Auto Start mode resumes. When returning to the main game, clicking anywhere on the screen stops the win ticker and displays the full prize.  &#10; &#10; &#10;BUTTONS: &#10; Info - Open the reference screen that describes the different game components. &#10;Auto Start / Stop - Spin the reels a number of times in succession. / End the active Auto Start reelspin mode. &#10; + and - buttons - Increase or decrease the number of successive spins made with Auto Start. &#10;Lines- Activate one more payline. &#10;LINE BET - Add a coin to the line bet. &#10;Bet Max - Activates all paylines with the current bet per line and spins the reels. &#10;Spin / Stop - Spin the reels. / During the reel spins the SPIN button changes into STOP. Clicking STOP ends the spin animation and immediately displays the spin results. Clicking Stop during the active Auto Start ends the spin animation and immediately displays the spin results. However, it does not end the Auto Start reelspin mode. &#10; &#10; &#10;NOTE ON DISCONNECTIONS: If you are disconnected from the Internet in the middle of the main game, the spin will be automatically completed. You can click the History button to see the outcome of your previous round after you log back into the casino. &#10; &#10;* If you are disconnected from the Internet during a bonus round or Free Games, you will be automatically directed back to the game after you log back into the casino so you can continue the game.  &#10; &#10;* If you are disconnected from the Internet during a spin using the Auto Start function, the spin will be automatically completed, but further spins will not automatically commence. You can click the History button to see the outcome of your previous round after you log back into the casino.&#10; &#10; &#10;NOTE ON MALFUNCTIONS: A malfunction voids all pays and plays.  &#10; &#10;This game has a Return to Player of 97.05%."/>  
	<phrase id="InsufficientBet" qa="true" text="Insufficient bet"/>  
	<phrase id="InsufficientBetBody" qa="true" text="Please place a bet equal to or greater than the minimum bet of %1."/>  
	<phrase id="InsufficientFunds" qa="true" text="Insufficient funds"/>  
	<phrase id="InsufficientFundsBody" qa="true" text="You do not have sufficient credits to place this bet. Please check your credit balance."/>  
	<phrase id="InvalidBetBody" qa="true" text="There are no bets to place"/>  
	<phrase id="InvalidBetTitle" qa="true" text="Invalid bet"/>  
	<phrase id="InvalidBetTypeBody" qa="true" text="One or more of your bets is incomplete. Please make sure you complete all your bets."/>  
	<phrase id="JackpotNotificationTitle" qa="true" text="Jackpots"/>  
	<phrase id="JackpotNotification" qa="true" text="Note that any Jackpots are shown and paid in your account currency."/>  
	<phrase id="loaderStart" qa="true" text="...loading"/>  
	<phrase id="loader1" qa="true" text="...loading graphics"/>  
	<phrase id="loader2" qa="true" text="...loading interface"/>  
	<phrase id="loader3" qa="true" text="...loading audio engine"/>  
	<phrase id="loader4" qa="true" text="...loading ambience engine"/>  
	<phrase id="loader5" qa="true" text="...loading EdGE components"/>  
	<phrase id="loaderFinish" qa="true" text="...loading complete"/>  
	<phrase id="MaxMultiRoundBody" qa="false" text="The maximum total stake permitted per round is %1. Please adjust your bet selection."/>  
	<phrase id="MaxSingleRoundBody" qa="false" text="The maximum total stake permitted per game is %1. Please adjust your bet selection."/>  
	<phrase id="MaxStakeTitle" qa="true" text="Maximum stake"/>  
	<phrase id="MaxStakeBody" qa="true" text="You have exceeded the maximum stake of %1 allowed for this bet."/>  
	<phrase id="MaxStakeAdjustedBody" qa="true" text="You have exceeded the maximum stake of %1 allowed for this bet. Your stake will now be adjusted to this amount for your approval. "/>  
	<phrase id="MultipleMaxStakeBody" qa="true" text="One or more of your bets exceeded the maximum stake allowed for that bet."/>  
	<phrase id="NANBody" qa="true" text="Please enter a numerical bet amount."/>  
	<phrase id="NANTitle" qa="true" text="Invalid bet"/>  
	<phrase id="Na" qa="true" text="n/a"/>  
	<phrase id="PlayForFun" qa="true" text="Play for Fun"/>  
	<phrase id="PlayForReal" qa="true" text="Play for Real"/>  
	<phrase id="SelectRealityBody" qa="true" text="Play with real funds from your account or virtual funds."/>  
	<phrase id="SelectRealityTitle" qa="true" text="Please select"/>  
	<phrase id="ServerConnectionErrorBody" qa="true" text="You have been disconnected from the gaming server. Please check your internet connection."/>  
	<phrase id="ServerConnectionErrorTitle" qa="true" text="Connection Error"/>  
	<phrase id="ServerError" qa="true" text="Server error"/>  
	<phrase id="ServerErrorTitle" qa="true" text="Error"/>  
	<phrase id="ServerJackpotErrorBody" qa="false" text="You have won the %1 Jackpot! Due to technical problems we are currently unable to add the jackpot to your bankroll automatically. To receive your prize, please contact customer support."/>  
	<phrase id="ServerNoGame" qa="true" text="Unable to retrieve game data."/>  
	<phrase id="ServerSuspensionBody" qa="true" text="The server is currently undergoing maintenance. Your game should resume automatically in a couple of minutes."/>  
	<phrase id="ServerSuspensionTitle" qa="true" text="Suspension of service"/>  
	<!-- Generic Server Error Messages Start -->  
	<phrase id="ServerBrowserError" qa="true" text="Sorry, there is no response from the gaming server."/>  
	<phrase id="ServerSessionLostBody" qa="true" text="Please log into your account. If you were previously logged in, your session may have expired."/>  
	<phrase id="ServerSessionLostTitle" qa="true" text="Session Lost"/>  
	<phrase id="ServerNoTitle" qa="true" text="This game is not currently available."/>  
	<phrase id="ServerNoFunds" qa="true" text="We have not been able to place your bet. Please check your updated balance."/>  
	<phrase id="ServerJackpotBalanceBody" qa="false" text="The jackpot balance has decreased and the amount displayed is no longer available. The jackpot balance will now update and your bet can be placed again."/>  
	<phrase id="ServerJackpotBalanceTitle" qa="false" text="Jackpot Balance"/>  
	<!-- Generic Server Error Messages End -->  
	<!-- End generic phrases -->  
	<!-- Start game specific phrases -->  
	<!-- i : Ishir	;	Msg : DisplayMessage	;	T : Title	;	M : Message -->  
	<phrase id="iMsgTOpenGame" qa="true" text="Open Game"/>  
	<phrase id="iMsgMOpenGame" qa="true" text="You have an open game. Click ok to continue. "/>  
	<phrase id="iMsgTInsufficientFunds" qa="true" text="Insufficient balance"/>  
	<phrase id="iMsgMInsufficientFunds" qa="true" text="You do not have sufficient credits to place this bet. Please check your credit balance"/>  
	<phrase id="iMsgTAutoplayInsufficientFunds" qa="true" text="Insufficient balance"/>  
	<phrase id="iMsgMAutoplayInsufficientFunds" qa="true" text="NOT ENOUGH BALANCE TO USE AUTOPLAY. PLEASE VISIT THE CASHIER AND MAKE A DEPOSIT"/>  
	<phrase id="iMsgTStakeLessThenAllowed" qa="true" text="Invalid Bet"/>  
	<phrase id="iMsgMStakeLessThenAllowed" qa="true" text="Please place a bet equal to or greater than the minimum bet of %1."/>  
	<phrase id="iMsgTMoreLessThenAllowed" qa="true" text="Invalid Bet"/>  
	<phrase id="iMsgMStakeMoreThenAllowed" qa="true" text="The maximum total stake permitted per game is %1 Please adjust your bet selection."/>  
	<phrase id="iMsgTNoResponseFromServer" qa="true" text="Server Error"/>  
	<phrase id="iMsgMNoResponseFromServer" qa="true" text="Empty Response XML from server. Click ok to resend request to server."/>  
	<phrase id="iMsgTNoOpenGame" qa="true" text="Invalid Game"/>  
	<phrase id="iMsgMNoOpenGame" qa="true" text="No open game present. Request server to open game."/>  
	<phrase id="iMsgTNoLanguageFailed" qa="true" text="Language Failed"/>  
	<phrase id="iMsgMNoLanguageFailed" qa="true" text="Error loading language file."/>  
	<phrase id="iMsgTAutoplayInvalidCount" qa="true" text="INVALID SPINS"/>  
	<phrase id="iMsgMAutoplayInvalidCount" qa="true" text="PLEASE ENTER THE NUMBER OF SPINS."/>  
	<phrase id="iMsgTAutoplaySpinsComplete" qa="true" text="AUTOPLAY STOPPED"/>  
	<phrase id="iMsgMAutoplaySpinsComplete" qa="true" text="AUTOPLAY STOPPED: |COUNT| SPINS COMPLETED."/>  
	<phrase id="iMsgTFreeGameMaxWinReached" qa="true" text="Maximum winning limit"/>  
	<phrase id="iMsgMFreeGameMaxWinReached" qa="true" text="You have exceeded the maximum possible winning limit for any one bet."/>  
	<phrase id="iMsgTBonusMaxWinReached" qa="true" text="Maximum winning limit"/>  
	<phrase id="iMsgMBonusMaxWinReached" qa="true" text="You have exceeded the maximum possible winning limit for any one bet."/>  
	<phrase id="iMsgMLoginFailed" qa="true" text="Please log into your account. If you were previously logged in, your session may have expired."/>  
	<phrase id="iMsgTLoginFailed" qa="true" text="Login Failed"/>  
	<phrase id="iMsgTGambleLimitReached" qa="true" text="GAMBLE LIMIT REACHED"/>  
	<phrase id="iMsgMGambleLimitReached" qa="true" text="YOU HAVE REACHED GAMBLE DOUBLE UP LIMIT."/>  
	<!-- i : Ishir	;	Err : Error -->  
	<phrase id="iErrSessionTimeOut" qa="true" text="Network connection failed. Unable to proceed request."/>  
	<!-- i : Ishir	;	GSM : Game Supportive Messages -->  
	<phrase id="iGSMGameInitialize" qa="true" text="CLICK SPIN TO START"/>  
	<phrase id="iGSMGamenNoWin" qa="true" text="CLICK SPIN TO START"/>  
	<phrase id="iGSMGameStarted" qa="true" text="GOOD LUCK!"/>  
	<phrase id="iGSMTriggerBonus" qa="true" text="YOU WIN BONUS!"/>  
	<phrase id="iGSMTriggerFreegameSelection" qa="true" text="%1 SCATTERS WIN %2 AND START FREE GAMES!"/>  
	<phrase id="iGSMSlotgameWinLine" qa="true" text="LINE %1 WINS %3"/>  
	<phrase id="iGSMSlotgameWinScatter" qa="true" text="%2 SCATTERS WIN %3 "/>  
	<phrase id="iGSMSlotgameTotalWin" qa="true" text="TOTAL WIN: %1"/>  
	<phrase id="iGSMBonusCollect" qa="true" text="COLLECT"/>  
	<phrase id="iGSMBetmaxInsufficientFunds" qa="true" text="CLICK SPIN TO START"/>  
	<phrase id="iGSMAutostartActive" qa="true" text="AUTOSTART ACTIVATED"/>  
	<phrase id="iGSMAutostartStopped" qa="true" text="AUTOSTART STOPPED"/>  
	<phrase id="iGSMFeatureWinBonus" qa="true" text="YOU WIN BONUS!"/>  
	<phrase id="iGSMFeatureWinFreegame" qa="true" text="%1 SCATTERS WIN %2 AND START FREE GAMES!"/>  
	<phrase id="iGSMFeatureWinExtraFreegame" qa="true" text="%1 SCATTERS WIN %2 AND %3 EXTRA FREE GAMES!"/>  
	<phrase id="iGSMInsufficientFunds" qa="true" text="INSUFFICIENT BALANCE"/>  
	<phrase id="iGSMSpinInsufficientFunds" qa="true" text="INSUFFICIENT BALANCE FOR THE REQUESTED BET"/>  
	<!-- End game specific phrases -->  
	<!-- Start generic vector text -->  
	<vector id="Win" qa="true" text="Win!"/>  
	<vector id="Unlucky" qa="true" text="Unlucky"/>  
	<vector id="Jackpot" qa="true" text="Jackpot!"/>  
	<!-- End generic vector text -->  
	<!-- Start  game specific vector text -->  
	<!-- End game specific vector text --> 
</languagepack>

